# OLEKSII CHEREVAN

Front-end developer



## **ABOUT ME**

Hi there! My name is Alex. I am a front-end developer. I am experienced in creating WEB applications. I was in a different front-end projects. In these projects my team and i used github and git flow. My first commercial application was made more than a year and a half ago. My aim is to improve my self as a software engineer.

P.S. I hope we will get it! Best wishes, Alex)



OleksiiCherevan@gmail.com



+380-99-56-1009



OleksiiCherevan.github.io



github.com/OleksiiCherevan

## **LANGUAGES**

**Ukrainian Native** 

**English** Intermediate

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Bachelor computer science (2019 - 2023) (2019 - 2023)

Institute Telecomunication and information

- Software engineer
- Front-end developer
- knowledge about how computer works, software tools, programming languages and patterns
- Work in a team
- Git / GitHub
- Java Script fundamental conceptions
- HTML / CSS
- Mongo DB

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Front-end developer, freelance (2021 - 2022)

Freelance, Software Engineer

- I have more than 15 finished projects and 100% positive marks
- I have been working as a front-end developer for almost 2 years.
- I am well experienced with HTML / CSS / SCSS / React / Redux / AJAX / Git / GitFlow
- I worked with RESTfull api, know CRUD operations
- I am familiar with building and deploying project on heroku or github pages.
- I have created a few pages from scratch.

#### Pet projects, Oleksii Cherevan (2021 - 2022)

My projects on github

- portfolio page- https://oleksiicherevan.github.io/
- exchanger- https://oleksiicherevan.github.io/exchanger/
- cafe design- https://github.com/OleksiiCherevan/simple-cafe/
- shop (get) https://oleksiicherevan.github.io/simple-fruit-shop/

#### **MY SKILLS**

#### Hard skills

- HTML / CSS / SCSS
- JavaScript / TypeScript
- Responsible design / adaptive design / Flex / Grid
- React / Redux
- Gulp / Webpack / Bubble
- Git / GitHub / GitFlow
- Figma
- MongoDB

#### Soft skills

- Self motivated
- Responsible
- Reliable
- I do my work properly
- Good communicative
- Friendly
- Team player

### **HOBBIES**









Music

Jogging

English

Conversation